Guide to the Intercollegiate Center for Nursing Education Director (Hilda Boerhave Roberts) Papers 1924-2001
Washington State University Libraries Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
- Courses, Series 6
  - Nursing 466: Nursing Leadership/Management--Concepts and Principles - Spring 1992 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 466: Nursing Leadership/Management--Concepts and Principles - Spring 1993 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 466: Nursing Leadership/Management--Concepts and Principles - Spring 1996 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 470: Introduction to Research - Fall 1972 to Spring 1973 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 470: Introduction to Research - Spring 1974 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 470: Introduction to Research - Spring 1975 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 477: Analysis of Health Care Ethics - Spring 1996 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 477: Analysis of Health Care Ethics - Spring 1997 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Fall 1968 to Spring 1969 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Fall 1970 to Spring 1971 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Fall 1971 to Spring 1972 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Fall 1972 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Spring 1973 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Fall 1973 to Spring 1974 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Winter 1973-1974 (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Fall 1974 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Winter 1974-1975 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Spring 1975 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Fall 1975 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Spring 1976 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Fall 1976 to Spring 1977 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Fall 1977 to Spring 1978 (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Fall 1978 to Spring 1979 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Fall 1979 to Winter 1980 (1 of 2) (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Fall 1979 to Winter 1980 (2 of 2) (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Spring 1980 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Summer 1980 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing - Fall 1980 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing, Archives - 1974 to 1980 (Box 151, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing, Archives - 1975 to 1979 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing, Archives - 1976 to 1980 (1 of 2) (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 480: Advanced Nursing, Archives - 1976 to 1980 (2 of 2) (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 481: Advanced Nursing Practicum - Fall 1970 to Spring 1971 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 481: Advanced Nursing Practicum - Fall 1971 to Spring 1972 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 481: Advanced Nursing Practicum - Fall 1972 to Spring 1973 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 483: Gerontological Nursing--Advanced Variable Credit - Spring 1992 (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 483: Gerontological Nursing--Advanced Variable Credit - Spring 1996 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 483: Gerontological Nursing--Advanced Variable Credit - Fall 1996 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 490: Special Topics--The Effects of Social Support During Pregnancy - Spring 1991 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 498: Special Topics--Analysis of Health Care Ethics - Spring 1991 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 498: Special Topics--Analysis of Health Care Ethics - Spring 1992 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 498: Nursing Practice--Critical Care - Fall 1992 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 498: Nursing Practice--Critical Care - Summer 1993 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 498: Nursing Practice--Critical Care - Summer 1994 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 498: Basic ECG Interpretation - Spring 1996 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 498: Basic ECG Interpretation - Spring 1997 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 498: Basic ECG Interpretation - Summer 1997 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 498: Laboratory Value Analysis and Interpretation - Fall 1997 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 499: Special Problems in Nursing - 1950 to 1971 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 499: Elective in School Nursing - Spring 1974 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 499: Elective in School Nursing - Spring 1975 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 499: School Nursing - Summer 1975 (Folder 17)
  - Nursing 499: School Nursing - Fall 1975 (Folder 18)
  - Nursing 499: School Nurse - Fall 1980 (Folder 19)
  - Nursing 499: School Nurse - Spring 1981 (Box 153, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 499: Special Syllabus - Spring 1982 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 499: Independent Study--Neonatal Critical Care - Spring 1989 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 499: Historical Trends in American Nursing - Spring 1992 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 499: School Nurse, Archives - 1973 to 1975 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 501: Nursing Theory and Research - Fall 1983 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 501: Nursing Theory and Research - Fall 1984 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 501: Nursing Theory and Research - Fall 1985 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 501: Nursing Theory and Research - Fall 1986 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 501: Nursing Theory and Research - Fall 1987 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 502: Nursing Theory and Research II - Spring 1985 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 502: Nursing Theory and Research II - Spring 1986 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 502: Nursing Theory and Research II - Spring 1987 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 502: Nursing Theory and Research II - Spring 1988 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 503: Theory Development and Evaluation - Spring 1985 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 503: Theory Development and Evaluation - Fall 1985 to Spring 1986 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 503: Theory Development and Evaluation - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 17)
  - Nursing 503: Theory Development and Evaluation - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 18)
  - Nursing 503: Theory Development and Evaluation - Fall 1990 (Folder 19)
  - Nursing 503: Theory Development and Evaluation - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 20)
  - Nursing 503: Theory Development and Evaluation - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 21)
  - Nursing 503: Theory Development and Evaluation - Spring 1995 (Folder 22)
  - Nursing 503: Theory Development and Evaluation - Spring 1996 (Folder 23)
  - Nursing 504: Methods of Nursing Research - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 24)
  - Nursing 504: Methods of Nursing Research - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 25)
  - Nursing 504: Methods of Nursing Research - Fall 1990 to Spring 1991 (Folder 26)
  - Nursing 504: Methods of Nursing Research - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 27)
  - Nursing 504: Methods of Nursing Research - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 28)
  - Nursing 504: Methods of Nursing Research - Fall 1994 to Spring 1995 (Folder 29)
  - Nursing 504: Methods of Nursing Research - Fall 1995 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 504: Methods of Nursing Research - Spring 1996 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 504: Methods of Nursing Research - Fall 1996 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 504: Methods of Nursing Research - Spring 1997 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 504: Methods of Nursing Research - Fall 1997 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 507: Professional Issues - Fall 1985 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 507: Professional Issues - Fall 1986 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 507: Professional Issues - Fall 1987 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 507: Professional Issues - Spring 1989 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 507: Professional Issues - Fall 1989 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 507: Professional Issues - Fall 1990 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 507: Professional Issues - Fall 1991 to Spring 1992 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 507: Professional Issues - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 507: Professional Issues - Summer 1993 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 507: Professional Issues - Fall 1993 - Spring 1994 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 507: Professional Issues - Fall 1994 - Spring 1995 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 507: Health Policy and Analysis - Fall 1995 (Folder 17)
  - Nursing 507: Health Policy and Analysis - Spring 1996 (Folder 18)
  - Nursing 507: Health Policy and Analysis - Fall 1996 (Folder 19)
  - Nursing 507: Health Policy and Analysis - Spring 1997 (Folder 20)
  - Nursing 507: Health Policy and Analysis - Fall 1997 (Folder 21)
  - Nursing 508: Strategies for Nursing Leadership - Spring 1985 (Folder 22)
  - Nursing 508: Strategies for Nursing Leadership - Fall 1985 to Spring 1986 (Folder 23)
  - Nursing 508: Strategies for Nursing Leadership - Spring 1987 (Folder 24)
  - Nursing 508: Strategies for Nursing Leadership - Spring 1988 (Folder 25)
  - Nursing 513: Nursing Service Administration--Theory and Role Analysis - Spring 1985 (Folder 26)
  - Nursing 513: Nursing Service Administration--Theory and Role Analysis - Spring 1986 (Folder 27)
  - Nursing 513: Nursing Service Administration--Theory and Role Analysis - Spring 1987 (Folder 28)
  - Nursing 513: Nursing Service Administration--Theory and Role Analysis - Spring 1988 (Folder 29)
  - Nursing 513: Nursing Service Administration--Theory and Role Analysis - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 30)
  - Nursing 513: Nursing Service Administration--Theory and Role Analysis - Fall 1989 (Folder 31)
  - Nursing 513: Nursing Service Administration--Theory and Role Analysis - Fall 1990 (Folder 32)
  - Nursing 513: Nursing Service Administration--Theory and Role Analysis - Fall 1991 (Folder 33)
  - Nursing 513: Nursing Service Administration--Theory and Role Analysis - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 34)
  - Nursing 513: Nursing Service Administration--Theory and Role Analysis - Fall 1995 (Folder 35)
  - Nursing 514: Personal Management in Nursing - Fall 1985 (Folder 36)
  - Nursing 514: Personal Management in Nursing - Fall 1986 (Folder 37)
  - Nursing 514: Personal Management in Nursing - Fall 1987 (Folder 38)
  - Nursing 514: Personal Management in Nursing - Spring 1989 (Folder 39)
  - Nursing 514: Personal Management in Nursing - Spring 1990 (Folder 40)
  - Nursing 514: Personal Management in Nursing - Spring 1991 (Folder 41)
  - Nursing 514: Personal Management in Nursing - Spring 1992 (Folder 42)
  - Nursing 514: Personal Management in Nursing - Spring 1993 (Folder 43)
  - Nursing 516: Practicum in Nursing Administration - Spring 1985 (Folder 44)
  - Nursing 516: Practicum in Nursing Administration - Spring 1986 (Folder 45)
  - Nursing 516: Practicum in Nursing Administration - Spring 1988 (Folder 46)
  - Nursing 516: Practicum in Nursing Administration - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 47)
  - Nursing 516: Practicum in Nursing Administration - Fall 1989 (Folder 48)
  - Nursing 516: Practicum in Nursing Administration - Fall 1990 (Folder 49)
  - Nursing 516: Practicum in Nursing Administration - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 50)
  - Nursing 517: Financial and Human Resources Management - Fall 1994 (Folder 51)
  - Nursing 521: Process of Teaching, Learning, and Evaluation in Nursing Education - Fall 1985 (Folder 52)
  - Nursing 521: Process of Teaching, Learning, and Evaluation in Nursing Education - Fall 1986 (Folder 53)
  - Nursing 521: Process of Teaching, Learning, and Evaluation in Nursing Education - Fall 1987 (Folder 54)
  - Nursing 521: Process of Teaching, Learning, and Evaluation in Nursing Education - Spring 1989 (Folder 55)
  - Nursing 521: Process of Teaching, Learning, and Evaluation in Nursing Education - Fall 1989 (Folder 56)
  - Nursing 521: Process of Teaching, Learning, and Evaluation in Nursing Education - Fall 1990 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 521: Process of Teaching, Learning, and Evaluation in Nursing Education - Fall 1991 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 521: Process of Teaching, Learning, and Evaluation in Nursing Education - Fall 1992 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 523: Nursing and Education--Theory and Role Analysis - Fall 1985 to Spring 1986 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 523: Nursing and Education--Theory and Role Analysis - Spring 1987 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 523: Nursing and Education--Theory and Role Analysis - Spring 1988 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 523: Nursing and Education--Theory and Role Analysis - Fall 1988 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 523: Nursing and Education--Theory and Role Analysis - Spring 1990 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 523: Nursing and Education--Theory and Role Analysis - Spring 1991 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 523: Nursing and Education--Theory and Role Analysis - Spring 1992 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 523: Nursing and Education--Theory and Role Analysis - Spring 1993 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 523: Nursing and Education--Theory and Role Analysis - Spring 1995 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 524: Multimedia Approaches to Instruction and Evaluation - Fall 1991 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 524: Multimedia Approaches to Instruction and Evaluation - Spring 1993 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 524: Multimedia Approaches to Instruction and Evaluation - Fall 1995 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 526: Practicum in Nursing Education - Spring 1985 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 526: Practicum in Nursing Education - Spring 1986 (Folder 17)
  - Nursing 526: Practicum in Nursing Education - Spring 1989 (Folder 18)
  - Nursing 526: Practicum in Nursing Education - Fall 1989 (Folder 19)
  - Nursing 526: Practicum in Nursing Education - Fall 1990 (Folder 20)
  - Nursing 526: Practicum in Nursing Education - Fall 1991 (Folder 21)
  - Nursing 536: Practicum in Adult Acute Care Nursing - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 22)
  - Nursing 536: Practicum in Adult Acute Care Nursing - Fall 1989 (Folder 23)
  - Nursing 536: Practicum in Adult Acute Care Nursing - Fall 1990 (Folder 24)
  - Nursing 536: Practicum in Adult Acute Care Nursing - Fall 1991 (Folder 25)
  - Nursing 536: Practicum in Adult Acute Care Nursing - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 26)
  - Nursing 537: Role Analysis--Advanced Practice - Fall 1995 (Folder 27)
  - Nursing 537: Role Analysis--Advanced Practice - Fall 1996 (Folder 28)
  - Nursing 537: Role Analysis--Advanced Practice - Fall 1997 (Folder 29)
  - Nursing 538: Acute Care Nursing--Concepts and Role Analysis - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 30)
  - Nursing 538: Acute Care Nursing--Concepts and Role Analysis - Spring 1992 (Folder 31)
  - Nursing 538: Acute Care Nursing--Concepts and Role Analysis - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 32)
  - Nursing 538: Acute Care Nursing--Concepts and Role Analysis - Summer 1993 (Folder 33)
  - Nursing 538: Acute Care Nursing--Concepts and Role Analysis - Fall 1994 (Folder 34)
  - Nursing 541: Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Fall 1988 (Folder 35)
  - Nursing 541: Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Fall 1989 (Folder 36)
  - Nursing 541: Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Fall 1990 (Folder 37)
  - Nursing 541: Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Summer 1991 (Folder 38)
  - Nursing 541: Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Fall 1991 (Folder 39)
  - Nursing 541: Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Fall 1992 (Folder 40)
  - Nursing 541: Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Spring 1994 (Folder 41)
  - Nursing 541: Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Spring 1995 (Folder 42)
  - Nursing 541: Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Fall 1995 (Folder 43)
  - Nursing 541: Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Fall 1996 (Folder 44)
  - Nursing 541: Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Fall 1997 (Folder 45)
  - Nursing 543: Concepts and Role Analysis in Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Spring 1990 (Folder 46)
  - Nursing 543: Concepts and Role Analysis in Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Spring 1991 (Folder 47)
  - Nursing 543: Concepts and Role Analysis in Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Spring 1992 (Folder 48)
  - Nursing 543: Concepts and Role Analysis in Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Fall 1992 (Folder 49)
  - Nursing 543: Concepts and Role Analysis in Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Fall 1993 (Folder 50)
  - Nursing 543: Concepts and Role Analysis in Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Fall 1994 to Spring 1995 (Folder 51)
  - Nursing 543: Concepts and Role Analysis in Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Spring 1996 (Folder 52)
  - Nursing 546: Practicum in Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Fall 1989 (Folder 53)
  - Nursing 546: Practicum in Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Fall 1990 (Folder 54)
  - Nursing 546: Practicum in Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Spring 1995 (Folder 55)
  - Nursing 546: Practicum in Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Fall 1995 (Folder 56)
  - Nursing 546: Practicum in Psychiatric/Mental Health Nursing - Fall 1996 (Folder 57)
  - Nursing 551: Community Health Nursing Concepts - Fall 1991 (Folder 58)
  - Nursing 551: Community Health Nursing Concepts - Fall 1992 (Folder 59)
  - Nursing 551: Community Health Nursing Concepts - Fall 1993 (Folder 60)
  - Nursing 551: Community Health Nursing Concepts - Fall 1994 (Folder 61)
  - Nursing 551: Community Health Nursing Concepts - Fall 1995 (Folder 62)
  - Nursing 551: Community Health Nursing Concepts - Fall 1996 (Folder 63)
  - Nursing 551: Community Health Nursing Concepts - Fall 1997 (Folder 64)
  - Nursing 552: Family Nursing in the Community - Fall 1994 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 552: Family Nursing in the Community - Fall 1995 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 553: Community and Family Analysis - Spring 1992 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 553: Community and Family Analysis - Spring 1993 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 554: Epidemiological Approaches to Community Health - Spring 1991 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 554: Epidemiological Approaches to Community Health - Spring 1992 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 554: Epidemiological Approaches to Community Health - Fall 1992 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 554: Epidemiological Approaches to Community Health - Fall 1993 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 554: Epidemiological Approaches to Community Health - Fall 1994 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 554: Epidemiological Approaches to Community Health - Fall 1995 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 554: Epidemiological Approaches to Community Health - Fall 1996 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 554: Epidemiological Approaches to Community Health - Fall 1997 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 556: Practicum in Community Health Nursing - Summer 1993 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 556: Practicum in Community Health Nursing - Fall 1993 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 556: Practicum in Community Health Nursing - Spring 1995 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 556: Practicum in Community Health Nursing - Spring 1996 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 561: Advanced Concepts in Transcultural Nursing - Fall 1985 (Folder 17)
  - Nursing 561: Advanced Concepts in Transcultural Nursing - Fall 1986 to Spring 1987 (Folder 18)
  - Nursing 561: Advanced Concepts in Transcultural Nursing - Fall 1987 to Spring 1988 (Folder 19)
  - Nursing 562: Advanced Health Assessment and Differential Diagnosis - Fall 1994 (Folder 20)
  - Nursing 562: Advanced Health Assessment and Differential Diagnosis - Fall 1995 (Folder 21)
  - Nursing 562: Advanced Health Assessment and Differential Diagnosis - Fall 1996 (Box 157, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 562: Advanced Health Assessment and Differential Diagnosis - Fall 1997 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 563: Pharmacology--Advanced Concepts and Practice - Fall 1994 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 563: Pharmacology--Advanced Concepts and Practice - Fall 1995 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 563: Pharmacology--Advanced Concepts and Practice - Fall 1996 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 563: Pharmacology--Advanced Concepts and Practice - Fall 1997 (Box 158, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 564: Health Promotion in Nursing Practice - Spring 1995 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 564: Health Promotion in Nursing Practice - Spring 1996 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 564: Health Promotion in Nursing Practice - Fall 1996 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 564: Health Promotion in Nursing Practice - Spring 1997 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 565: Information Management for Nursing Practice - Fall 1994 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 565: Information Management for Nursing Practice - Fall 1995 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 565: Information Management for Nursing Practice - Spring 1996 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 565: Information Management for Nursing Practice - Fall 1997 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 566: Community Analysis and Program Planning - Spring 1994 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 566: Community Analysis and Program Planning - Spring 1995 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 566: Community Analysis and Program Planning - Spring 1996 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 566: Community Analysis and Program Planning - Spring 1997 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 567: Primary Care--Adults and Elders - Spring 1995 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 567: Primary Care--Adults and Elders - Spring 1996 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 567: Primary Care--Adults and Elders - Spring 1997 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 568: Primary Care--Infants, Children, and Adolescents - Fall 1995 (Box 159, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 568: Primary Care--Infants, Children, and Adolescents - Fall 1996 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 568: Primary Care--Infants, Children, and Adolescents - Fall 1997 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 569: Primary Care--Family - Fall 1995 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 569: Primary Care--Family - Spring 1996 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 569: Primary Care--Family - Spring 1997 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 571: Advanced Concepts in Nursing I - Fall 1986 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 571: Advanced Concepts in Nursing I - Fall 1987 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 572: Advanced Concepts in Adult Health and Illness II - Spring 1985 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 572: Advanced Concepts in Adult Health and Illness II - Spring 1986 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 572: Advanced Concepts in Adult Health and Illness II - Spring 1987 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 572: Advanced Concepts in Adult Health and Illness II - Spring 1988 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 574: Clinical Nursing - Fall 1985 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 574: Clinical Nursing - Fall 1986 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 574: Clinical Nursing - Fall 1987 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 575: Advanced Concepts in Nursing I - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 16)
  - Nursing 575: Advanced Concepts in Nursing I - Fall 1989 (Folder 17)
  - Nursing 576: Advanced Concepts in Nursing II - Spring 1989 (Folder 18)
  - Nursing 576: Advanced Concepts in Nursing II - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 19)
  - Nursing 576: Advanced Concepts in Nursing II - Spring 1991 (Folder 20)
  - Nursing 576: Advanced Concepts in Nursing II - Spring 1992 (Folder 21)
  - Nursing 576: Advanced Concepts in Nursing II - Spring 1993 (Folder 22)
  - Nursing 577: Analysis of Health Care Ethics - Spring 1993 (Folder 23)
  - Nursing 577: Analysis of Health Care Ethics - Spring 1995 (Folder 24)
  - Nursing 577: Analysis of Health Care Ethics - Spring 1996 (Folder 25)
  - Nursing 581: Advanced Pathophysiology I - Spring 1988 (Folder 26)
  - Nursing 581: Advanced Pathophysiology I - Fall 1988 to Spring 1989 (Folder 27)
  - Nursing 581: Advanced Pathophysiology I - Fall 1989 (Folder 28)
  - Nursing 581: Advanced Pathophysiology I - Fall 1990 (Folder 29)
  - Nursing 581: Advanced Pathophysiology I - Fall 1991 (Folder 30)
  - Nursing 581: Advanced Pathophysiology I - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 31)
  - Nursing 581: Advanced Pathophysiology I - Fall 1994 (Folder 32)
  - Nursing 581: Advanced Pathophysiology I - Fall 1995 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 581: Advanced Pathophysiology I - Fall 1996 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 581: Advanced Pathophysiology I - Fall 1997 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 582: Advanced Pathophysiology II - Spring 1989 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 582: Advanced Pathophysiology II - Fall 1989 to Spring 1990 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 582: Advanced Pathophysiology II - Spring 1991 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 582: Advanced Pathophysiology II - Fall 1992 to Spring 1993 (Folder 7)
  - Nursing 582: Advanced Pathophysiology II - Spring 1995 (Folder 8)
  - Nursing 582: Advanced Pathophysiology II - Spring 1996 (Folder 9)
  - Nursing 582: Advanced Pathophysiology II - Spring 1997 (Folder 10)
  - Nursing 583: Gerontological Nursing - Spring 1989 (Folder 11)
  - Nursing 583: Gerontological Nursing - Fall 1992 (Folder 12)
  - Nursing 583: Gerontological Nursing - Fall 1994 (Folder 13)
  - Nursing 583: Gerontological Nursing - Spring 1996 (Folder 14)
  - Nursing 592: School Nursing I - Fall 1991 (Folder 15)
  - Nursing 592: School Nursing I - Fall 1992 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Nursing 594: School Nursing II - Spring 1993 (Folder 2)
  - Nursing 595: Internship - Fall 1995 (Folder 3)
  - Nursing 595: Internship - Spring 1997 (Folder 4)
  - Nursing 595: Internship - Fall 1997 (Folder 5)
  - Nursing 598: Special Topics - Spring 1986 (Folder 6)
  - Nursing 598: Special Topics - Spring 1987 (Folder 7)